A Guide to the Papers of Edward E. Younger, 1937-1979
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- VI. Student Papers- Virginia History
  - Rhodes, William: "The Patrician and the Politician" 1965 (Box 54)
  - Ritsch, Frederick: "John Letcher and ...Slavery in the ...Election of 1858-1859" 1956 (Box 54)
  - Ritchie, John: "The Gubernatorial Campaign in Virginia in 1901" 1954 (Box 54)
  - Robertson, William: "The Cockade City, 1860-1864" 1968 (Box 54)
  - Roebuck, James: "The U.S. and World Affairs: The View from Virginia, 1945-1950" 1966 (Box 55)
  - Saunders, Robert: "Crime and Punishment in Early National America" 1973 (Box 55)
  - Saunders, Robert: "Virginia Populism" n.d. (Box 55)
  - Schwartz, Karen: "The Virginia WCTU, Women Move into the World" 1977 (Box 55)
  - Semes, Robert: "The Constitution and the New Deal" 1963 (Box 55)
  - Severn, Frank: "Virginia's Reaction to the Blair Education Bill, 1880-1890" 1952-1953 (Box 55)
  - Scouten, Lee: "The Menhaden Industry in Lancaster" 1975 (Box 55)
  - Shackelford, Virginius: "The 'Liberal' Movement in Virginia Politics" 1968 (Box 55)
  - Shelton, Charlotte: "Virginia Politics and Woman Suffrage" n.d. (Box 55)
  - Shibley, Ronald: "Electoral Reform in Virginia, 1937-1950" 1967 (Box 55)
  - Shibley, Ronald: "Electoral Reform in Virginia, 1950-1966" 1968 (Box 55)
  - Shibley, Ronald: "Progressive Reform or Machine Politics" n.d. (Box 55)
  - Shifflelett, Crandall: "Virginia History Since 1865, A Bibliography" 1970-1971 (Box 55)
  - Siff, Brigette: "Shifting Party Politics in Virginia" 1977 (Box 55)
  - Smith, Beatrice: "The Farmers' Alliance and the Race Issue" n.d. (Box 55)
  - Smith, Beatrice: "The Campaign of 1893" n.d. (Box 55)
  - Smith, James: "The Virginia Constitutional Convention of 1867-1868" 1955 (Box 55)
  - Spurlock, Stanley: "John Mercer Langston, Negro's Friend or Foe?" 1955 (Box 55)
  - Steele, Patta: "The Origins of a Victory" 1977 (Box 55)
  - Steele, Patta: "The Rise of the Readjusters in the Central Shenandoah Valley" n.d. (Box 55)
  - Suggs, Henry: "Editorial Reflections of Race Relations" 1971 (Box 55)
  - Simmons, Dennis: "Shenandoah National Park and Skyline Drive" 1974 (Box 55)
  - Stevenson, Nora: "General John Daniel Imboden" 1976 (Box 55)
  - Tanner, Douglas: "Guides to Archival and Manuscript Sources" 1977 (Box 56)
  - Tarter, Brent: "Harry Byrd for President, 1932" 1973 (Box 56)
  - Tarter, Brent: "Conservative Critique of the New Deal" 1973 (Box 56)
  - Tarter, Brent: "The Rise of the Byrdocracy" n.d. (Box 56)
  - Tarter, Brent: "Notes on Norfolk" n.d. (Box 56)
  - Taylor, Robert: "The Jamestown Tercentennial" 1955 (Box 56)
  - Taylor, Robert: "The Old Dominion and New Freedom" n.d. (Box 56)
  - Thompson, Paul: "Strike of 1930-1931" 1963 (Box 56)
  - Trice, F.: "The C.S.S. Albemarle" 1959 (Box 56)
  - Underhill, Marjorie: "Virginia's May Day Parade [1905]" 1952 (Box 56)
  - Vance,?: "Thomas Jefferson Randolph" n.d. (Box 56)
  - Vipperman, Carl: "The Coattail Campaign" 1963 (Box 56)
  - Vogt, George: "Election of T.B. Stanley" 1970 (Box 56)
  - Vogt, George: "Republicanism" n.d., 2 folders (Box 56)
  - Wagenblast, Dennis: "Early Congressional Career of Carter Glass, 1900-1912" 1973 (Box 56)
  - Waits, John: "Roanoke's Tragedy: The Riot of 1893" 1971 (Box 56)
  - Wallace, C. Southall: "E.R. Cocke" 1957 (Box 56)
  - Wiley, Wayne: "The Educational Philosophy of Edwin Anderson Alderman" 1972 (Box 57)
  - Willis, Stanley: "Gubernatorial Campaign and Election, Virginia, 1921" 1963 (Box 57)
  - Wilton, Barry: "The Virginia Gubernatorial Campaign of 1873" 1976 (Box 57)
  - Winter, Warren: "The Phelps-Stokes Fellowship" 1971 (Box 57)
  - Winters, Marvin: "Benjamin Franklin Buchanan" n.d. (Box 57)
  - Winters, Marvin: "Benjamin Franklin Buchanan, Tax Reformer, and Legislative Giant, 1859-1932" n.d. (Box 57)
  - Wray, Francis: "The Ku Klux Klan in Virginia, 1920-1930" n.d. (Box 57)
  - Wynes, Charles: "O'Ferrall and the Virginia Gubernatorial Election of 1893" 1955 (Box 57)
  - Zimmerman, Harry: "The Organization and its Harry Byrds: Faith of the Father Living Still?" 1972 (Box 57)
  - [?]: "The Political Career of George Campbell Peery" n.d. (Box 57)
  - [?]: "The Political Career of Henry D. Flood" n.d. (Box 57)
  - Historiography and Bibliography
    - Agrarianism, Agriculture, and Populism 1967-1973 (Box 57)
    - American Architecture 1972-1974 (Box 57)
    - American Religion 1970-1971 (Box 57)
    - Black History 1967-1970, n.d. (Box 57)
    - Business and Industry 1961-1974 (Box 57)
    - The Cold War 1968-1972, n.d. (Box 58)
    - Communism and Liberalism 1968-1973 (Box 58)
    - Diplomacy and Party Politics n.d. (Box 58)
    - Diplomatic History 1963-1973, n.d. (Box 58)
    - Education (by Wayne Wiley) 1971 (Box 58)
    - Eisenhower Era 1972-1973, n.d. (Box 58)
    - Fellowship for Reconciliation n.d. (Box 58)
    - Gilded Age 1970-1972, n.d. (Box 58)
    - Immigration 1967-1971, n.d. (Box 58)
    - Imperialism 1964-1973 (Box 58)
    - Indians (American) 1968-1969, n.d. (Box 58)
    - Intellectual History 1971-1974, n.d. (Box 58)
    - Labor 1964-1971 (Box 58)
    - Mason, Lucy Randolph 1969 (Box 58)
    - New Deal 1964-1973, n.d. (Box 58)
    - The New South 1969-1973 (Box 59)
    - The New West and the Frontier 1967-1974 (Box 59)
    - The Nineteen Twenties 1962-1973 (Box 59)
    - Panama Canal 1963 (Box 59)
    - Political History 1968-1974 (Box 59)
    - Progressive Movement 1962-1974 (Box 59)
    - "Road to Pearl Harbor" n.d. (Box 59)
    - Reconstruction 1969-1974, n.d. (Box 59)
    - "Southern History, 1877-1913, A Critical Essay on Recent Works," by Charles B. Dew n.d., 2 folders (Box 59)
    - "Spanish-American War: Reaction of American Protestant Journalism" by Nicholas Wood 1971 (Box 60)
    - Truman Era 1964-1973, n.d. (Box 60)
    - Urban History 1968-1973 (Box 60)
    - War of 1812 n.d. (Box 60)
    - "The Women's Movement" by Carol Clare Chowdry 1968 (Box 60)
    - World War I Intervention 1959-1972 (Box 60)
    - "World War II, Impact on American Society," by John Crocker 1971 (Box 60)
    - Miscellaneous 1961-1962, n.d. (Box 60)
  - Miscellaneous Subjects
    - Alfred, Francis: "The Brussels Conference" 1967 (Box 60)
    - Allen, Carlos: "Blaine Defends the Alaska Fur Seal Herd" 1947 (Box 60)
    - Anderson, Arthur: "The Burundia Affair" 1970 (Box 60)
    - Arbena, Joseph: "The Affair of the 'Virginius'" 1961-1962 (Box 60)
    - Arbena, Joseph: "The Magdelena Bay Resolution" 1962 (Box 60)
    - Ball, Harry: "Seward, Grant, and Napoleon III" and "Seward and Grant: Mexico, Reconstruction..." 1977, 1978 (Box 60)
    - Barnard, William: "Edward R. Stettinius, Jr.: Formative Influences" 1966 (Box 61)
    - Barnard, William: "Edward R. Stettinius, Jr. and the Reorganization of the State Dept." 1966 (Box 61)
    - Barrow, Robert: "William Howard Taft and the First Panama Canal Crisis" n.d. (Box 61)
    - Borus, Daniel: The Popular Novelist as Social Observer...Edward Payson Roe" n.d. (Box 61)
    - Brent, Robert: "The U.S. Peace Commission at Ghent, 1814" 1947 (Box 61)
    - Bressler, Ann: Changes in Women's Mission Work in the Nineteenth Century" 1976 (Box 61)
    - Bressler, Ann: "The Impact of Social Gospel on the ...Female Role" 1977 (Box 61)
    - Britt, S.S.: Nicaragua Coal Companies" 1948 (Box 61)
    - Bull, Cornelius: "Miles Poindexter and the League of Nations" 1956 (Box 61)
    - Burton, W.J.: "Jay Gould" 1954 (Box 61)
    - Campbell, J.M.: "The Nationalization of America's U.N. Policy, 1944-1945" n.d. (Box 61)
    - Campbell, Thomas: "The Inter-American System and the Birth of the United Nations" n.d. (Box 61)
    - Caravati, Charles: "Coxey's Army" 1959 (Box 61)
    - Carpenter, Charles: "The Confederate States Cruiser Georgia" 1956 (Box 61)
    - Cha-Tsu Siu, Victoria: "Sino-American Relations, 1882-1885" 1977 (Box 61)
    - Corbitt, Duvon: "Cuban Revisionist Interpretations of Cuba's Struggle for Independence" 1962 (Box 61)
    - Curry, Peter: "The Democratic Party and the Constitution During the ...Trial of Andrew Johnson" n.d. (Box 61)
    - Dillon, Robert: "The Invasion of Puerto Rico" 1963, n.d. (Box 61)
    - Dixen, Walter: "The Relations Between...Jefferson Davis and ...Joseph Eggleston..." 1959 (Box 61)
    - Doss, Richard: "The Antislavery Crusade of Edward Coles..." 1951 (Box 61)
    - Doss, Richard: "Federal Development of overland Routes..." 1953 (Box 61)
    - Downing, Bruce: "...Korea: The Joint Chiefs of Staff and ...MacArthur" 1970 (Box 61)
    - Eddy, Nancy: "Cuban-American Relations During the Spanish American War" 1972 (Box 61)
    - Edwards, Laverne: "William E. Dodd, Ambassador to Germany" 1963 (Box 61)
    - Ettari, Robert: "Dr. Gatling and His Gun" 1955 (Box 61)
    - Falk, Charles: "The Money and Banking Question, 1865-1913" 1972 (Box 61)
    - Farrier, Paul: "Confederate Hospitals" 1956 (Box 62)
    - Fifer, Francis: "George E. Spencer" 1953 (Box 62)
    - Fitzpatrick, Peter: "The Trescott Mission, 1881-1882" 1970 (Box 62)
    - Flayhart, William: "Some Aspects of the Wilkes Cruise" 1967 (Box 62)
    - Fowler, Richard: "The Communications Revolution...1865-1900" 1974 (Box 62)
    - Friedlander, Blaine: "A Visit to the U.S. by the Emperor of Brazil" 1948 (Box 62)
    - Gilliam, Bates: "View of U.S. House of Representatives Toward the Samoan Question" 1948 (Box 62)
    - Graves, John: "Election Reform and Negro Disfranchisement: An Arkansas Case Study" 1970 (Box 62)
    - Gray, John: "Richard Hathaway Edmonds" 1952 (Box 62)
    - Hall, Claude: Dissertation Outline on "Abel Parker Upshur," and "Perspectives of Midwestern Historian on Foreign Problems" n.d. (Box 62)
    - Hayman, Robert: "The First Modern War" [The U.S. Civil War] 1959 (Box 62)
    - Hammersmith, Jack: "John Watson Foster and the Hawaiian Question" and "The Appointment of ...Foster as Secretary of State" 1966 (Box 62)
    - Harper, James: "The Recognition of Obregon by the U.S." and "Hugh Scott and the Mexican Crisis of 1916" n.d. (Box 62)
    - Hawkes, Robert: "The Klan: Its Purpose and Appeal" 1965 (Box 62)
    - Hays, Hubbard: "The Matonuska Valley Colonization Project" n.d. (Box 62)
    - Hendrick, Alice: "The Fellowship of Reconciliation, 1915-1934" n.d. (Box 62)
    - Henriques, Peter: "An Argument that the Constitution was Anti-Slavery" 1968 (Box 62)
    - Henson, Edward: "Roosevelt's Intervention in the Crisis at Munich" 1958 (Box 62)
    - Herring, George: "The Struggle for Preparedness, 1914-1915" 1961 (Box 62)
    - Herring, George: "Lend-Lease to Russia and the Origins of the Cold War" 1968 (Box 62)
    - Herring, John: "..The Tsarist and Soviet Slave Labor Systems" 1959-1960 (Box 62)
    - Hogan, Bart: "George Davis Herron" 1956 (Box 62)
    - Hohner, Robert: "James Cannon,-Salisbury and Randolph-Macon" 1975 (Box 62)
    - Holt, Michael: "The Death of the Second American Party System" n.d. (Box 63)
    - Hough, Leslie: "U.S. Diplomacy and Party Politics, 1865-1925" 1970 (Box 63)
    - Hughes, Thomas: "Southern Inventive Genius" 1954 (Box 63)
    - Hunt, Edward: "The Biological Study of Human Evolution" 1950 (Box 63)
    - Hunter, Robert: "Reluctant Reformers" 1971 (Box 63)
    - Ivey, Willie: "The Status and Conditions of Blacks...During the Gilded Age" n.d. (Box 63)
    - Jellison, Charles: "Mr. Fessenden Casts His Vote" 1955 (Box 63)
    - Jensen, Russell: "The Nation Looks at Hitler" 1965 (Box 63)
    - Jones, Archer: "Confederate Strategy from Shiloh to Vicksburg" 1959 (Box 63)
    - Jones, Robert: "Submarines in the Confederacy" 1955 (Box 63)
    - Jones, Robert: "Herbert Croly" 1959 (Box 63)
    - Jordan, Laylon: "The Liberal Image of Mussolini" 1967 (Box 63)
    - Kavanaugh, James: "Organized American Labor, 1916-1924" 1956 (Box 63)
    - Klingaman, Will: "The Rhineland Negotiations at the Paris Peace Conference, 1919" 1973 (Box 63)
    - Klingaman, Will: "The American Press Response to the Suez Crisis" 1974 (Box 63)
    - Lane, Rebecca: "General Samuel Cooper" 1956 (Box 63)
    - Laney, Frank: "Recognition of the ...African International Association by the U.S." n.d. (Box 63)
    - Large, Jack: "Sanford: The Town, The Man" 1955 (Box 63)
    - Laughram, Joseph: "The Liberty League" 1956 (Box 63)
    - Laushey, David: "Ceylonese-American Relations and the Oil Controversy of 1961-1964" 1964 (Box 63)
    - Levin, Robert: "The Muscle Shoals Controversy: Southern Reaction..." 1965 (Box 63)
    - Levinson, Peter: "...Lindbergh's Decoration by Nazi Germany..." 1956 (Box 63)
    - Lewis, Helen: "The Subcultures of the Southern Appalachians..." 1967 (Box 63)
    - Lowenstein, Susan: "Poland 1945: American Decisions and Compromise" 1971 (Box 63)
    - Lowery, Charles: "Matthew Josephson: An Appraisal" 1963 (Box 63)
    - Marmon, Lee: "Thomas Fortune Ryan and ...Corporate Materialism in American Culture" 1974 (Box 64)
    - Marowitz, Matthew: "The Effect of the McGuffey Readers on ...the Gilded Age" n.d. (Box 64)
    - Matray, James: "The Press and Foreign Policy in the Korean War" 1973 (Box 64)
    - Matzko, John: "The Founding of the American Bar Association" 1975 (Box 64)
    - Maynard, Chris: "The Ch'ing and the Foreigner" 1970 (Box 64)
    - McGunegle, David: "Anglo-American Relations, 1938" 1971 (Box 64)
    - Melzer, John: "The Alien Vote and Grandfather Clause Issues in the Alabama Convention of 1901" n.d. (Box 64)
    - Moreau, John: "Randolph Silliman Bourne" 1963 (Box 64)
    - Morrison, John: "Roosevelt: The Man" 1959 (Box 64)
    - Moss, Robert: "Wilbur Joseph Cash" 1965 (Box 64)
    - Mumper, James: "Evolutionism in America" and "A Search for Standards" 1961-1962 (Box 64)
    - Patterson, Flora: "Utah and the Civil War" 1954-1955 (Box 64)
    - Pitt, Thomas: "The Santos Affair" 1971 (Box 64)
    - Poarch, John: "American Reaction During the Great Red Scare of 1919-1920" n.d. (Box 64)
    - Poindexter, Harry: "The Muckrakers" and "Dollar Diplomacy in the Orient" 1953, n.d. (Box 64)
    - Risjord, Norman: "Conservatives, War Hawks, and the Nation's Honor" 1959-1960 (Box 64)
    - Ritch, William: "The State-War-Navy...Committee and Post-WW II Policy for Japan" 1972 (Box 64)
    - Ritch, William: "Nixon's Security Affairs Decision-Making Process" 1972 (Box 65)
    - Ritch, William: On Post WW II Japan" 1975 (Box 65)
    - Ritch, William: "The Standing Liason Committee" n.d. (Box 65)
    - Ritsch, Frederick F.: "The Russo-German Rapprochement" 1956 (Box 65)
    - Robe, Robert: "The Ambassador Refused" [re Edward Dodd] 1956 (Box 65)
    - Robinson, John: "The Emma Mine Scandal and General Schenck" n.d. (Box 65)
    - Robidoth, Richard: "Steps Leading to U.S. Recognition of U.S.S.R." 1965 (Box 65)
    - Roebuck, James: "The South and World Affairs" 1967 (Box 65)
    - rose, Willie Lee: "Masters without Slaves" n.d. (Box 65)
    - Rucker, Warren: "...Diplomacy in U.S.-Japanese Exchange of Prisoners" 1969 (Box 65)
    - Runge, William: "Leroy Pope Walker: The...Confederate War Department" 1955 (Box 65)
    - Rutman, Darrett: "The War Crimes Trial of Henry Wirz" 1956 (Box 65)
    - Saeli, Jeffrey: "The Taft Katsura Agreement" 1965 (Box 65)
    - Scanlon, James: "H.L. Mencken and the Politics of the Nineteen Twenties" 1965 (Box 65)
    - Scharth, Elizabeth: "Slavery in Brazil and the United States" 1974 (Box 65)
    - Scott, Patricia: "Business Attitudes Toward Religion in the 1920's" 1954 (Box 65)
    - Scribner, [?]: "Some notes on Recent American Tariff Policy" n.d. (Box 65)
    - Shapiro, Samuel: "John Brown and Fidel Castro" n.d. (Box 65)
    - Speidel, G.C.: "Visiting Statesman in Florida, 1876" 1953 (Box 65)
    - Stokes, William: "Pork Diplomacy, An American-German Controversy, 1879-1891" 1948 (Box 65)
    - Sturgis, Stewart: "The Arena and A. Mitchell Palmer" 1956 (Box 65)
    - Swofford, Don: "Balloon Framing" 1974 (Box 65)
    - Sydenham, [?]: "Sacco and Vanzetti" n.d. (Box 65)
    - Tanner, Douglas: "American Public Opinion and the Munich Crisis" 1967 (Box 65)
    - Tanner, Douglas: "The Democratic Party and the Philippines, 1898-1921" 1968 (Box 65)
    - Tarter, Brent: "The Farmer Become Businessman...1865-1896" 1974 (Box 65)
    - Taylor, Robert: "The Price Grant, A Confederate Colonization Attempt" n.d. (Box 66)
    - Thomas, John: "Admiral Rickover And the Nautilus" 1956 (Box 66)
    - Thompson, Paul: "The Third Corps at Mine Run" n.d. (Box 66)
    - Tupper, Lamont: "George Kennan" 1964 (Box 66)
    - Twichell, Curtis: "The Spice of Spencer" 1955 (Box 66)
    - Vance, Joseph: "William Gibbs McAdoo" n.d. (Box 66)
    - Weir, Leslie: "The Lasker Revolution" 1948 (Box 66)
    - West, Franklin: "Bonnet at the Quai D'Orsay" n.d. (Box 66)
    - Wine, Beverley: "Woodrow Wilson" 1959 (Box 66)
    - Wood, Robert: " The Masses and the Art of World-Building" 1974 (Box 66)
    - Wright, J. Leitch: "Humanity and Diplomacy: ...the Geneva Convention of 1864" 1955 (Box 66)
    - Young, Lowell: Franklin D. Roosevelt and Imperialism" 1967 (Box 66)
    - [?]: "Thomas F. Millard: American Journalist in Shanghai" n.d. (Box 66)
    - [?]: "Sino-American Relations 1931-1933: Frank Ross McCoy" n.d. (Box 66)
    - [?]: "The Place of the Saint Pierre-Miquelon Invasion in Anglo-American-Free French Relations, 1940-1943" n.d. (Box 66)
- VII. Photographs
  - 4 photographs of "Ash Lawn" ca. 1890-1910 (Box 66)
  - 2 photographs of UVa Naval War College ca. 1940-1945, n.d. (Box 66)
  - 1 photograph of UVa History Dept. Faculty ca. 1965 (Box 66)
  - 52 photographs from Mss/Archives files selected for Albemarle, Jefferson's County but not used n.d. (Box 66)
  - 11 photographs from files of the Daily Progress selected for Albemarle, Jefferson's County, but not used n.d. (Box 66)
  - 6 photographs from files of the Chamber of Commerce selected for Albemarle, Jefferson's County, but not used n.d. (Box 66)
  - 25 photographs from published sources selected for Albemarle, Jefferson's County but not used n.d. (Box 66)
  - 4 photographs from various sources selected for Albemarle, Jefferson's Countyn.d. (Box 66)
  - Pictures of John A. Kasson n.d. (Box 66)
- VIII. Student Subject Files
  - Adams, G. Stuart 1967-1968 (Box 67)
  - Aldred, Frank K. 1964-1967 (Box 67)
  - Alexander, James L. 1974-1975 (Box 67)
  - Alsop, Pamela Rock n.d. (Box 67)
  - Altizer, James E. 1965 (Box 67)
  - Anchors, Clanton 1962-1968 (Box 67)
  - Anderson, Arthur E., III 1969-1970 (Box 67)
  - Arbena, Joseph L. 1963-1966 (Box 67)
  - Armstrong, W. Donovan 1965 (Box 67)
  - Barnard, William D. 1966-1977 (Box 67)
  - Bell, Robert T. 1968-1973 (Box 67)
  - Blanton, S. Walker, Jr. 1965-1969 (Box 67)
  - Bochnowski, John F. 1964-1968 (Box 67)
  - Boney, Francis Nash 1960-1977 (Box 67)
  - Boudreau, Richard 1973-1975 (Box 67)
  - Brandt, Paul W. 1965 (Box 67)
  - Breeden, Jim 1960-1973 (Box 67)
  - Brent, Irving 1963 (Box 67)
  - Brown, Robert 1972-1973 (Box 67)
  - Bugg, James L. 1966-1976 (Box 67)
  - Buker, Margaret J. 1971 (Box 67)
  - Bull, Neil 1959-1969 (Box 67)
  - Buni, Andrew 1966-1975 (Box 67)
  - Burke, Arthur L. 1965 (Box 67)
  - Burnette, Ollen L., Jr. 1962-1969 (Box 68)
  - Burnette, Ollen L., Jr. 1970-1978 (Box 68)
  - Butt, Lucille D. 1965 (Box 68)
  - Cahill, Audry 1972 (Box 68)
  - Calhoun, Walter T. 1957-1970, 2 folders (Box 68)
  - Campbell, Otho C. 1969-1979 (Box 68)
  - Campbell, Thomas Moody, Jr. 1959-1978 (Box 68)
  - Carter, Herbert F., Jr. 1965 (Box 68)
  - Chaffin, David G. 1965 (Box 68)
  - Chambers, Nellie A. 1965 (Box 68)
  - Chang, Chun-Shu 1963 (Box 68)
  - Cheek, William Francis, III 1960 Oct.-1968 Mar. (Box 68)
  - Chowdry, Carol Clare 1968-1973 (Box 68)
  - Chowdry, P.S. 1967-1974 (Box 68)
  - Clayton, Thomas 1962-1968 (Box 68)
  - Clement, Patsy Jane 1965 (Box 68)
  - Clough, Lynndon 1962-1964 (Box 68)
  - Cole, Carol 1971-1972 (Box 68)
  - Cooper, Fred A. 1965 (Box 68)
  - Corley, Robert G. 1962-1979 (Box 69)
  - Costello, George W. 1965 (Box 69)
  - Cotton, Roosevelt 1977-1978 (Box 69)
  - Cox, Harold 1962 (Box 69)
  - Cullinane, Robert 1971 (Box 69)
  - Crampton, Richard H. 1962-1965 (Box 69)
  - Cranberg, Lawrence 1969 (Box 69)
  - Crane, Robert I. 1964 (Box 69)
  - Crawley, William B., Jr. 1968 July-1979 Feb. (Box 69)
  - Crellin, Mark Robert 1971-1972 (Box 69)
  - Cullop, Charles Painter 1959-1970 (Box 69)
  - Dierenfield, Bruce 1977-1979 (Box 69)
  - Donnelly, James Baker 1963-1979 (Box 69)
  - Dorwart, Jeffrey M. 1965-1966 (Box 69)
  - Doss, Richard B. 1973-1978 (Box 69)
  - Downing, Bruce E. 1970 (Box 69)
  - Dungee, Mary W. 1965 (Box 69)
  - Dunn, Robert L. 1975-1977 (Box 69)
  - Eastburn, Charlie 1965 (Box 69)
  - Ebner, Michael 1965-1968 (Box 69)
  - Elish, Raymond D. 1965 (Box 69)
  - Ely, James W., Jr. 1967-1976 (Box 69)
  - Ferrell, Henry Clifton, Jr. 1960-1972 (Box 69)
  - Finnigan, James Thomas 1974-1975 (Box 69)
  - Fitzpatrick, Peter Bryan 1969-1970 (Box 69)
  - Flayhart, William Henry, III 1966-1967 (Box 69)
  - Fry, Joseph A. 1968-1978, 2 folders (Box 70)
  - Fulks, Robert W. 1971 (Box 70)
  - Gay, Thomas 1966-1975 (Box 70)
  - Gibb, Nancy (Eddy) 1970-1971 (Box 70)
  - Gibbs, Daniel 1962-1977 (Box 70)
  - Gillespie, Dan n.d. (Box 70)
  - Gioia, Sandra D. 1973-1978 (Box 70)
  - Goolrick, Chester A. 1968 (Box 70)
  - Gordon, Vesta 1969-1977 (Box 70)
  - Graves, John William 1969-1979 (Box 70)
  - Griffing, Daniel J. 1966-1967 (Box 70)
  - Grubbs, Frank 1960-1975 (Box 70)
  - Gruen, Eric 1961-1964 (Box 70)
  - Gusler, Jesse J. 1965 (Box 71)
  - Hall, Alvin L. 1966-1976 (Box 71)
  - Hall, Claude H. 1968 (Box 71)
  - Hammersmith, Jack 1967-1978 (Box 71)
  - Hammett, Hugh Bernard n.d. (Box 71)
  - Herndon, George Melvin 1963 (Box 71)
  - Herring, George 1968-1977 (Box 71)
  - Hess, Gary R. 1962-1978 (Box 71)
  - Haley, Anna L. 1965 (Box 71)
  - Harper, James W. 1967-1978 (Box 71)
  - Harrison, James P. Jr. 1960-1962 (Box 71)
  - Harrison, Joseph Hobson 1965 (Box 71)
  - Hartje, Robert 1963-1966 (Box 71)
  - Hawkes, Robert T., Jr. 1967-1975 (Box 71)
  - Heblich, Fred 1972 (Box 71)
  - Heinemann, Ronald L. 1968-1978 (Box 71)
  - Henriques, Peter R. 1968-1976 (Box 71)
  - Henson, Edward L. 1963-1975 (Box 72)
  - Herrick, Walter R., Jr. 1960-1967 (Box 72)
  - Hiatt, Rex C. 1973-1975 (Box 72)
  - Hickin, Patricia 1961-1973 (Box 72)
  - Hiller, Jack Lewis 1965-1966 (Box 72)
  - Himmelein, Frederick T., III 1968 (Box 72)
  - Hohner, Robert A. 1972 (Box 72)
  - Holland, Arthur S. 1965 (Box 72)
  - Holt, Wythe Whiting, Jr. 1967-1979 (Box 72)
  - Honesty, Charles H. 1965 (Box 72)
  - Hopewell, John S. 1962-1976 (Box 72)
  - Hough, Leslie S. 1970 (Box 72)
  - Hunley, John D. 1968 (Box 72)
  - Huppe, Alexander 1971 (Box 72)
  - Husted, Robert L. 1966-1969 (Box 72)
  - Jackson, Austin L. 1965 (Box 72)
  - Jellison, Charles 1967 (Box 72)
  - Jensen, Russell 1965-1966 (Box 72)
  - Johnson, Glenn L. 1965 (Box 72)
  - Johnson, L.W. 1965 (Box 72)
  - Jones, Robert R. 1960-1972 (Box 72)
  - Jordan, Layton Wayne 1968-1975 (Box 72)
  - Judkins, Shirleen 1976-1977 (Box 73)
  - Kirby, Jack T. 1965-1979 (Box 73)
  - Lampard, Eric 1965 (Box 73)
  - Landon, John C. 1977-1979 (Box 73)
  - Larsen William Edward 1960-1977 (Box 73)
  - Lawhorn, Jack K. 1965 (Box 73)
  - Leebrick, Gloria 1975 (Box 73)
  - Lester, Malcolm Nicholas n.d. (Box 73)
  - Lewis, Martin Deming 1962-1963 (Box 73)
  - Lowe, Richard G. 1965-1968 (Box 73)
  - Lowenstein, Susan 1971 (Box 73)
  - McCasland, S.V. 1971 (Box 73)
  - McKenney, Ida E. 1965 (Box 73)
  - McPherson, James 1968 (Box 73)
  - Maddex, Jack 1965-1971 (Box 73)
  - Makaritis, Elizabeth 1960-1961 (Box 73)
  - Manning, Lawrence C. 1965 (Box 73)
  - Marshall, Rudolph R. 1965 (Box 73)
  - Martin, Lewis 1974-1975 (Box 73)
  - Matheny, Emma C. 1965 (Box 73)
  - Melzer, John T.S. 1964 (Box 73)
  - Mertz, Richard Rolland 1963 (Box 73)
  - Miles, Robert 1973 (Box 73)
  - Milstead, Don Burnell 1965 (Box 73)
  - Moore, James Tice 1966-1978 (Box 73)
  - Moore, John Hammond 1960-1977 (Box 74)
  - Moreau, John 1964-1978 (Box 74)